<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>coreos on Je pense donc je suis</title>
    <link>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/tags/coreos/</link>
    <description>Recent content in coreos on Je pense donc je suis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 18:22:48 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/tags/coreos/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kubernetes on Coreos</title>
      <link>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/post/kubernetes-on-coreos/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 18:22:48 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/post/kubernetes-on-coreos/</guid>
      <description>Kubernetes is an open-source system for automating deployment, scaling, and management of containerized applications.&#xA;I just follow the guide of CoreOS + Kubernetes Step By Step to deploy Kubernetes cluster on CoreOS.&#xA;Although this guide is detailed, there&amp;rsquo;s still something that will cause misunderstanding and should be paid close attention to. So this post is to help you better follow the guide and setup Kubernetes.&#xA;First of all, according to CoreOS cluster architectures, the CoreOS + Kubernetes Step By Step guide is for Easy development/testing cluster or Production cluster with central services, however, what I have is a Small cluster which was set up in the way Setup CoreOS Cluster with Static IPs, that will make some difference to ETCD_ENDPOINTS environment variable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setup Coreos Cluster With Static Ip</title>
      <link>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/post/setup-coreos-cluster-with-static-ip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 18:22:33 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/post/setup-coreos-cluster-with-static-ip/</guid>
      <description>We have talked about how to setup a CoreOS cluster in my previous post: Setup CoreOS Cluster Manually with VirtualBox. However, as we setup the cluster in VirtualBox, which uses DHCP as default, the etcd2 may not work when VM&amp;rsquo;s IP changed.&#xA;So in this article I&amp;rsquo;ll tell you how to upgrade your cluster and enable the VMs use static IPs instead of DHCP.&#xA;Setup Static IP First of all, make sure your cluster node VM uses the bridge connection type (as default), that will enable the connection between outer world, as we are not going to set IP tables.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Worldpress in Coreos Cluster Using Fleet</title>
      <link>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/post/deploy-worldpress-in-coreos-cluster-using-fleet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2016 18:22:13 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/post/deploy-worldpress-in-coreos-cluster-using-fleet/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I would like to tell you how to deploy a simple WorldPress service with MySQL database in CoreOS cluster in 3 minutes. You may reference my previous blog to setup a CoreOS cluster locally if you don&amp;rsquo;t have one.&#xA;Ok, ssh to one of your cluster node, let&amp;rsquo;s start.&#xA;Step 1 Create MySQL service Create a unit file mysql.service&#xA;1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 [Unit] Description=MySQL DataBase After=etcd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Setup Coreos Cluster Manually with Virtualbox</title>
      <link>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/post/setup-coreos-cluster-in-virtualbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2016 18:21:53 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://wenfeng-gao.github.io/post/setup-coreos-cluster-in-virtualbox/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I wanted to set up a tiny CoreOS cluster in my laptop, the good news is that with several commands and the existed Vagrantfile offered by the CoreOS official guide, we can setup a cluster in minutes; the bad news is that I don&amp;rsquo;t like everything perfectly done by Vagrant like a magic box, I want to do it total manually, and there&amp;rsquo;s no tutorial as I expected.&#xA;So as I made it work finally, it&amp;rsquo;s time to share with others.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
